

Profile

I have big experience in my life, graduated as an engineer in renewable sources of energy, then I moved to Poland and living here at this moment working in factories. Now i decide, i have to change my life and as i wanted before, went into the IT specialty. I finished courses as a front-end HTML/CSS+JS developer and continue to improve my skills in this way.

Employment History

C+P at Welder Operator, Legnica

September 2022

Production Operator at Lear Corporation, Legnica

August 2020 — June 2022

Production Operator at Voss Automotive Poland Sp. o.o., Legnica

June 2019 - April 2020

Engineer at JSC "Khersonoblenergo", Kherson

May 2017 — June 2018

Education

Bachelor, Kherson National Technical University, Kherson September 2010 — June 2014

Specialist, Kherson National Technical University, Kherson

September 2014 - June 2015

Courses

Front-end (HTML/CSS +JS), Lemon School

October 2022 — January 2023

English, Private teacher

October 2014 - April 2015

Details

Kherson

Ukraine

+48 733 819 952

alex_eastwoody@yahoo.com

Date of birth

19-06-1993

Links

Portfolio

Linkedin

Skills

HTML & CSS

JavaScript

Bootstrap

Google Search

Hobbies

Japanese Culture, Cars, Gaming, Sport

Languages

English

Ukrainian

Russian

Polish